thebigfreechiplist.com 2019-04-05

# Privacy Policy - TheBigFreeChipList.com

TheBigFreeChipList.com created this Web Site Privacy Policy (the "Privacy Policy") to give you confidence as you visit and use TheBigFreeChipList.com (the "Website"), and to demonstrate our commitment to fair information practices and the protection of privacy. TheBigFreeChipList.com respect and is committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy lets you know how your personal information is processed and used.

**Acceptance of Agreement**

  * By Accessing or using our site or accessing any content from or on the Site, you are indicating that you have read, understand and agree to be bound by these terms of service and agreeing to comply with and be bound by the following terms of use. Please read carefully and review the following terms and conditions (“Terms of Service”) our End User License Agreement and our Privacy Policy, which may be found at our site and which is incorporated by reference into these Terms of Service and is a part of this Agreement. These Terms of Service govern your access to and use of the Site and Application and, except as otherwise provided in these Terms of Service, all text, graphics, images, music, software, audio, video, information or other materials available through the Site (“Content”), and constitute a binding legal agreement between you and the site.
  * If you do not agree to these terms, you have no right to access or use the Site or any content of this site.
  * We reserve the right, at our sole discretion, to modify or terminate the Site or from time to time to modify these Terms of Service, without specific notice to you. The latest Agreement will be posted on the Site, and you should review this Agreement prior to using the Site. By continuing to access or use the Site after we have posted a modification on the Site, you are indicating that you agree to be bound by the modified Terms of Service.

**Personal Information**

We pay meticulous attention to your personal privacy thus you can feel free to use TheBigFreeChipList.com site without giving any personal information or data. Although we will appreciate if you contact us or submit feedback with your name and contact information, you are more than welcome to remain anonymous. If you are willing to provide your personal information, TheBigFreeChipList.com has security measures in place to prevent the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information that TheBigFreeChipList.com obtains from you, but TheBigFreeChipList.com makes no assurances about its ability to prevent any such loss, misuse, to you or to any third party arising out of any such loss, misuse, or alteration.

**Business Relationships**

TheBigFreeChipList.com has links to several Web sites and is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of other Web sites we linked to.

**Cookies**

TheBigFreeChipList.com developed tools to control popup windows and IA (interstitial advertisements) as the purpose of these tools is to minimize the amount of advertisements the user watch with on a given visit to TheBigFreeChipList.com

**The California Online Privacy Protection Act (OPPA)**

We value your privacy and we have taken the precautions to be in compliance with the OPPA. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

**The Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA)**

We do not collect any information from anyone under 18 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 18 years old or older.

**Online Privacy Policy Only**

Our online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

**Third party links**

We may include or offer third party products or services on TheBigFreeChipList.com. These offers and third party websites have separate and independent privacy policies and Terms & Conditions. Therefore, we have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these websites.

**Mailing List**

If you will join our mailing list, we will keep your email address and any demographics information you volunteer strictly confidential. We will never give or sell your email address or any information about you to anyone else. Please keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information that information can be collected and used by others. You are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your online information. Please be careful and responsible whenever you're online.

**Contact Details**

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of TheBigFreeChipList.com, you can contact us by sending email to: support @ thebigfreechiplist.com
